[Music]
good morning family and
friends on behalf of the family I'd like
to welcome you here to the celebration
of life for Shan Sheldon
aders the family would like to express
their gratitude and thanks for your
support and your presence here this
morning additionally I just ask that uh
to continue to solicit your prayers over
the days weeks months and years to come
for what Paul describes in the church
that what he wrote to the church at
Philippi as a peace that surpasses all
understanding family because I won't
have a moment to share Reflections I
just want to share sh with you a very
short reflection that I have of Shawn
when I think of Shawn I think of him in
many roles father son husband brother uh
but when I think of Sean one text comes
to mind for me because we worked out in
the same gym and so I would see Sean
very fluently and with ease walk through
and have keen interest in everybody
who's working
out and I'm an introvert so I look and
say wow Sean's talking to everybody but
I think of Matthew
and Matthew
5:116 says let your light so shine
before men that they will see your good
works and glorify your father who is in
heaven and I think of Sean who very
genuinely and
enthusiastically shared his faith with
everybody and I'll miss
him I'm going to hone in just for a
minute on the program uh ask you to do a
couple things for those who are
participating today I would ask that you
pay close attention to when your time
comes up uh and then move kind of
expeditiously here to the rostom and
make your comments uh one other thing
the family has asked and looking forward
to your comments and your Reflections if
you look in your bulletin you'll see
special memories that's an opportunity
for you to share your Reflections and
who Shawn was to you and what he meant
to you they're asking two things they
very much want to hear your thoughts but
they're also asking that you keep them
concise and I'm going to say around two
minutes now I'm going to help you if you
get a little off but I'm going to ask
you really stick to that two-minute
timeline so that we can get through the
service in a timely
manner final thing I'll share is that
and I'll step down and let the pastors
come up in times like these it's an
opportunity for us to know God in a more
deep way and I'm asking us to each pray
for this family pray for their peace
pray for support pray that they feel
God's love with that we will ask the
pastors to come up both Pastor Jose and
Pastor Kim and and offer us the opening
prayer
pastors good
morning if you look in your program I am
not Pastor Abraham
jwes um but
um just want to offer a special prayer
of comfort
for the family and the friends who are
here and I'll pray in English and Pastor
Kim we pray in
Korean our father and our
God today we come to you in the name of
Jesus Christ Our
Lord thanking you Lord for the life that
you gave
Shan and the privilege you gave us to
get to know him and his family
today Lord we pray in a special way that
you may come very close to the
family surround them with your love and
comfort give them
strength not only today Lord but in the
days and months
ahead be with your
children his wife
Veronica and all the family members who
are here
[Music]
we thank you that we have the hope that
Jesus Christ is coming
soon and we shall
be
together never to separate
anymore so in that promise we
rest we believe and we thank you in
Jesus name amen
[Music]
Peron
for
[Music]
for for
for
I
pray in Jesus
name amen
[Music]
um so Uncle Shawn was always the um the
poet type and
um he often told me that his favorite
biblical character was um the the
character of David um and because of
that he he very much loved the um the
Psalms so it's only fitting that uh we
read his favorite verse for scripture
reading uh it's found in Psalm 91 um if
you guys want to
follow he who dwells in the secret place
of the most high shall abide under the
shadow of the alight
I will say of the Lord he is my refuge
and my Fortress my God in him I will
trust surely he will deliver You From
The Snare of the Fowler and from the
perilous pestilence he shall cover you
with his feathers and under his wings
you shall take refuge your his truth
shall be your shield and
buckler you shall not be afraid of the
terror by night nor of the arrow that
flies by day nor of the presence that
walks in darkness nor of Destruction
that lays waste at Nord day a th
thousand may fall at your side and
10,000 at your right hand but it shall
not come near you only with your eyes
shall you look and see the reward of the
wicked because you have made the Lord
who is my refuge even the most high your
dwelling place no evil shall befall you
nor shall any plague come near your
dwelling
for he shall give his angels charge over
you to keep you in all your ways in
their hands they shall
bear bear you up lest lest you dash your
foot against a
stone you shall tread upon the lion and
the coroba the Young Lion and the
serpent you
shall you shall trample Under Foot
because he has set his love upon me
therefore I will deliver him I will set
him on high because he has known my name
he shall call upon me and I will answer
him I will be with him in trouble I will
deliver him and honor him with long life
I will satisfy him and show him my
salvation thank you all
my name is Paulo Esposito I currently
Pastor the fredicksburg 7 Day Adventist
Church and I've been given the honor of
sharing Sha's life sketch with you if
you have a program you can open it to
the very first page to your right and
you can follow along as I
read Shan Sheldon Maurice Mayors
affectionately known as Al and Shawn was
born on August 11
1973 to Ronnie and Erica Myers he was
the youngest of four brothers and in
1978 when Shan was four years old they
moved to Brooklyn New York and he was
introduced to the hip-hop culture and
began practicing
gymnastics after he and his brother Al
along with tamarat became deeply
involved in the martial arts Sean
learned the art of wing Chu from his
uncle Tony and together with his brother
tamarat and several F friends Mark sha
and ahed formed the Ninja Alliance and I
understand they're not to be confused
with the Ninja Turtles that was another
Alliance all together with a very
similar purpose where they imagined
themselves as ninjas training to save
the world from an imminent attack they
purchased all kinds of ninja suits and
weapons using the house wall for tar
target practice with ninja throwing
darts and spikes much to their parents'
dismay I am sure of that and then I can
imagine sea smiling and then he would
probably get away with everything
because that's the smile that Sean sea
had in junior high he became popular
after winning a beat boox competition
defeating the school's top beat boxer
this is not physical box and these are
sounds just if you're wondering
performing a triple beat with his voice
box from that point on everyone in the
school. junior high loved Shawn in 1988
the family moved to Fredericksburg
Virginia where Shawn entered the 10th
grade at Chancellor high school and met
his lifelong friend Sha paard Sha his
brother and Pard would go on from hip
hop group called to form a hip-hop group
called Vex one and the Boogie monsters
Sean and his brother were the dancers
and Vex was was The Lyricist Sean's
popularity continued to grow due to his
dancing ability picking up more friends
he graduated from Chancellor high in
1991 and then attended Virginia Union
University where he forged more lifelong
friendships and met another lifelong
friend gerlin Paul this group of friends
referred to the themselves as the
ex-men again not to be confused with the
X-Men franchise that later came along
which many believe their success was
attributed to the original X-Men to whom
they still owe royalties but they
haven't been paid two years later the
hip-hop Group by then called The Boogie
monsters consisting of Shan Pard Vex
mandoo M Shan Jedi minri and Ivor known
as Yoda was signed by Emmy records the
group gained popularity for its unique
style of hip-hop with jedy minri
infusing reggae lyrical content during
the time sha was introduced to the
Seventh Day Adventist message which
eventually led him to leave the group
and pursue Ministry in 1998 he enrolled
at Oakwood University in Huntsville
Alabama studying health for one semester
before transferring to Harland College
in Virginia to continue his health
studies he also formed more lifelong
friendships at both transitions in it
was at Harland college that he met his
future wife Veronica Sean and Veronica's
Love Story began in the heart of
ministry where they shared passion for
serving others and Blossom into a
beautiful ROM
romance they exchanged vows on September
5 2004 embarking on a journey filled
with love Faith and service Sean's
commitment to Ministry led him to led
him from Health Ministry to pastoral
roles deeply impacting the life of those
he encountered he also dedicated his
time as direct support professor
professional working with individuals
with intellectual disabilities his
compassion and dedication Shone through
in both his career earning him the love
and respect of clients and members of
the Nova 7th Day Adventist Church Sean's
infectious smile and joyful laughter
touched the hearts of everyone around
him Shawn lives behind his beloved
family Veronica and three children Sarai
Savannah and Judah he's also survived by
his parents Ronnie and Erica Brothers
Tony and Pam Rowan and Stacy Ivor and
Aton nieces nephews Aunts Uncles cousins
and a multitude of close friends other
relatives and church family as we grieve
the loss of Shawn we hold on to the hope
of the second coming of Jesus eagerly
anticipating the day we will be re
United with our dear Shawn and until
that day comes may he rest peacefully
amen
[Music]
we're very honored to be able to be here
in behalf of the Myers family and I have
wonderful memories my name is Betsy
Mayer I've been the the coral director
at Harland college for over 40 years and
Sean was one of my students have very
warm memories of him my music class and
we're very glad to be able to share a a
piece today that brings you straight
into the heart of God and the promises
from
scripture do not
let your
heart be
troubl neither
Let It
Be
Afraid put your
trust in
God
believe in
him who are M to not be
afraid do not
let your
heart be
TR NE
let
araid
araid put your
TR God
[Music]
you
are not
[Music]
beid in my father's house are many rooms
his
promises are
true I will go to prepare a place
prepare a place for you
come
again I will come
[Applause]
again yes I'll come
again come for
you for
you do
not your
heart be TR
[Music]
[Applause]
be
PR would your
trust in
God
believe in
me you are M do not
be
afraid ofid
you are
mine do not
be
[Music]
afraid do not
let your heart beid
[Music]
am
[Applause]
good
morning my name is jino Kim friend of
Sean
and today we gather here to celebrate
the life of an extraordinary man
Sean a humble servant of God a powerful
preacher and a dear friend who
profoundly impacted my life and my
family and the lives of many
others I first met Sean over 20 years
ago at Harland
college at the time I was a new doctor
from Argentina
navigating the challenges of
transitioning to life in the states
teaching Anatomy physiology and learning
English yes in this
order first day I
met 1999 in a
springtime and over the years our
friendship grew he became my pastor at
the Nova Korean church I attended with
my
family every Sabbath we eagerly
anticipated his sermons not just for the
wisdom they brought but because Sean
lived what he
preached he was
humble loving and
steadfast he never judged but always
encouraged he was constantly lifting
others up
praying for them and guiding them closer
to
Christ he exemplified the words of
Proverbs
16:32 whoever is slow to anger is better
than the mighty and he who rules his
Spirit than he who take a city Sean was
a man of
self-control with
Temperance he he faced many challenges
at church with calmness and faith never
allowing anger or Pride to take hold of
him in a world that often glorifies
outward strength Sean reminded us that
the true strength lays in the ability to
rule one's spirit and to reflect the
character of Jesus in all things one of
the most remarkable things about Sean
was his
prayer his prayer life Sean didn't just
pray he prayerfully
Faithfully prayed for every single one
of us I know he had many
booklets where he wrote down answered
prayers when sea
realized song's family
at our church was having a baby Sean
humbly confessed that he had been
praying for Dr son and his family twice
a day for
years and
avoid having a sermon about Father and
Son relationship from the
Bible to be sensitive to those family
that's who Sean was a man who didn't
just preach about prayer but lived it he
believed in prayer and rejoiced when God
answered prayers big and
small I have so many cherished memories
of Sean one Sabbath morning he preached
a sermon that was so
wonderful I knew I supposed to say the
political politically correct phrase
praise the Lord but I did
I I teased him Sean Sean bro you are way
better than
ior he he smiled he smiled and I pr and
replied wisely really do you think
so that was who he was always thoughtful
always humble always reflecting another
memory that brings a smile to my face is
my yearslong mission to convince him to
play the trumpet Sean played a guitar
but I tell him bro this is the trumpet
Jesus
plays there is no better instrument than
the trumpet then yeah I I convince him
and we practice every Sabbath
afternoon but all of this the sermons
the laughter the memories should be put
into a larger perspective
lived as someone who understood what we
all must remember that we are not of
this
world we belong to the economy of heaven
where everything comes from God flows
through Jesus and is given to us this
truth guided Sean's life and it is a
truth he embodied every day Sean didn't
just talk about God's Kingdom
he lived it his life reflected the words
Jesus shared in the
mountain Sean was poor in spirit for his
is the Kingdom of Heaven Shan mourned
and he was
conforted Shawn was Meek and he will
inherit the earth sha hungered and
thirsted for righteousness and he was
filled Shan was merciful
and he will be shown Mercy Shan was pure
in heart for he will see God he was a
peacemaker for he is a child of God
Shawn was persecuted because of
righteousness for his is the Kingdom of
Heaven Sean was a blessed
man merciful Meek pure in heart
a
peacemaker and someone who hungered and
thirsted for
righteousness his life was a living
testimony of the Living
Word and as we remember Sean today I
want to tell you
something if you want to see Sean
again make sure your heart is right with
God be humble be merciful be
truthful live as lived with a heart
fully surrendered to Christ reflecting
his love in every
action until we meet again in King in
his kingdom my dear friend I will carry
your lessons your prayers your smile and
your love in my heart thank you for
being such a profound blessing in my
life and for showing us all what it
truly means to ref reflect Jesus
[Applause]
[Music]
good morning everyone and thank you for
being here today to celebrate the life
of our uncle Shan for those of you who
don't know me my name is Madison and I
am the oldest daughter of Uncle Sean's
brother
Rowan if there's one thing I cherish
more than anything it's the closeness of
my family for most of my life I've lived
within 15 minutes of Uncle Sean Auntie
Ronica and my cousins and because of
this I have countless memories with
Uncle sha over the past 23 years
memories that will live in my heart and
mind
forever Uncle Sean was always there when
you needed him I distinctly remember how
in elementary middle school if I ever
needed to be somewhere he made sure I
got there although he wasn't the best
driver I'll never forget how he used to
sit so reclined in his seat that he
could barely see the road and he'd be
really confused when people were honking
at him but he was crossing the devil
yellow
lines um but somehow we always made it
where we needed to be in one piece so I
have no
complaints when I was old enough to
drive Uncle Shawn didn't think twice
about letting me borrow his is cherry
red Jeep I can't say that I would have
had the same trust in a newly licensed
16-year-old but I'll always appreciate
that he
did running into Uncle sea always put a
smile on my face I lost count of how
many times I'd be driving and look over
on the road only to find him right next
to me I especially loved running into
him at the gym um especially on the days
I didn't feel like working out because
his positive energy was always
contagious everyone at the gym knew him
um and he was always chatting between
said quick to brag to anyone around that
I was his niece before giving me a kiss
on the forehead and finishing his
workout Uncle Shawn loved his family
more than anything even when he was sick
he was always thinking about others in
April he texted me saying he had asked
the resident physicians at VCU if they
knew me but they said they didn't I
hadn't even started medical school but I
admired the thought this past November
he texted me to ask if I'd be in DC
during election week and whether it
would be safe and what we're probably
some of the most difficult moments of
his life he was so worried about
everyone
else one of the things I admired the
most about Uncle Sean was his love for
God and his dedication to sharing the
word in 2014 when I decided to be
baptized I was so excited when Uncle sha
offered to guide me through the process
by doing my baptismal lessons several
years later he did the same for my
little brother Kaden there's no one else
we would have rather gone through that
process with and it's something we will
both be grateful for forever he was so
knowledgeable about the word and was
always willing to help others understand
it Uncle sha was always there he was
truly like a second father to me he was
at my high school volleyball
championship game my Governor School
graduation my high school graduation my
college graduation it's still hard for
me to wrap my mind around the fact that
he won't be at Cadence High School
graduation or my Medical School
Graduation though he's no longer
physically with us I know he will live
on in our hearts for the rest of our
time on this Earth on behalf of myself
my little brother and all of our cousins
Uncle Sean we love you we miss you we
admire you and we will carry your love
and character in our actions for the
rest of our lives until we meet
[Applause]
again morning
everyone my uh my name's Larry I'm uh
Uncle Sean's cousin through Mar or I'm
sorry nephew through marriage um I did
not have the privilege of knowing Shawn
for a lifetime he became my uncle
through marriage to Crystal the thing is
though you didn't need a lifetime to get
to know Uncle Shawn all you needed it
was a conversation or two to know
exactly who he was what you saw is what
you got and if you listen to his words
you would have received much much more I
met Uncle Shan at a Christmas party in
2020 over at my uncle rowen's and Aunt
Stacy's home it was actually my first
time meeting most of Crystal's local
family this was no ordinary family this
home was full of excitement with loud
conversations and laughter everyone
there were all wearing silly oversized
Christmas hats for family pictures I
would later find out that this was a
family tradition one of many most of
Crystal's Family were towering over me
as some of them stature wise are much
closer to God than
I everyone was wearing covered masks so
imagine trying to get to know your
future wife's family in these
circumstances I was overwhelmed and
didn't really know what to say or do the
truth was I didn't really have to say or
do anything there were no
expectations it was a come as you are
are feeling throughout the home a man
grabbed my arm gently pulled me in close
to him and said put on this hatman I did
as I was told introduced myself and he
did the same we prepared ourselves and
our silly hats to pose for the family
picture and the friendly man and the
friendly man I had just met named Shawn
whispered in my ear are you sure you're
ready for all this Larry
lion I answered in complete confidence I
was born
ready little did I know the people in
that picture would be the most
influential and loving people in my life
today I love you Uncle
Sean and I will always carry you with me
thank
[Applause]
you good morning
everyone today I want to share a few
words about my amazing
Uncle if you ever had the privilege of
being around him you know exactly what
I'm talking about Uncle Shawn had the
gift of laughter he could light up any
room not once did I ever leave his
presence without cracking up no matter
what was going on in life he had the
amazing ability to use humor to get
through anything and that was part of
his
Aura one thing I'll miss the most is our
family
traditions um going to the gym together
whenever I visited my family here it was
something we always did and it made
those times together even more
special
St every year on my birthday day my
uncle would call me and share memories
with me he shared how he would carry me
on his shoulders down the streets of
Brooklyn when I was a baby when he and
my dad lived together he really embraced
his role as our uncle those moments will
stay with me
forever I remember the day that I told
him I was going to be a mom he was so so
happy for
me and he couldn't get over the fact
that JD Wy was
his nickname for
me was going to be a
mom I
remember getting a text from him the
next day
he had sent a list of vitamins and
supplements he
thought he thought I should take for the
baby but that's just who he was he was
always there with advice and always
there to listen and with a beautiful
prayer I admire that so much about him
he knew just how to be a source of
wisdom and comic
relief Uncle Sean's love his laughter
and his prayers were constant in my life
I'm going to miss those random calls
asking the most random questions or
sharing something funny that made me
laugh out
loud life without him is going to be
tough but I find peace that knowing one
day I'll see him
again I am so incredibly thankful that
he was my my
uncle he was truly one of a kind and I
know I'll carry his spirit with me
forever until we meet
[Applause]
again so when I was a kid um
and yeah we're talking like late 90s
early
2000s um uncle Shawn
he um he played the guitar even from
back then and I just remember as a kid
thinking that was just the coolest thing
ever and you know we're we come from a
very musically inclined family and
um
I I just remember he was the only one in
our family at least that I knew that
played guitar and so I just thought I
was like wow when like when I grow up
I'm want to play guitar like that too
and
um I eventually uh picked up guitar I
started learning it and Uncle sea is
like a large he's a large part of the
reason why um I picked up
guitar
and
um I I remember when I got when I when I
finally got good enough
when I finally got got good enough at
Guitar um every time I'd come around
here for the holidays and he would just
take me out
and we would go to Guitar Center and we
would just spend hours in Guitar Center
and I remember he would pick up like
the most obnoxious looking
guitar and and we're talking like like a
two $3,000 guitar and it looked so
obnoxious like you would just never
picture Uncle Shawn playing it but he
would just pick it up and play it for
hours and we would just hang out in
Guitar Center and that was just that was
kind of like our thing I don't think he
did that with any of the other cousins
at
least so yeah we had a thing uh we
listened to music
we love listening to seal radio head
Coldplay Bob
Marley and so many others so many other
artists and
um yeah I'm just I'm gonna miss
that that animated Uncle sea that
creative Uncle sea and he's always going
to live in our
hearts thank you
[Applause]
if you'll bear with me a little bit I
have a
cough um unlike many of our cousins my
siblings and I didn't have the privilege
of growing up in Virginia with the rest
of the
family while that meant we didn't share
in the everyday moments with Uncle Sea
The Memories We do have are Priceless
ones we wouldn't trade for anything in
the
world I could stand here and recount
countless stories of his humor
spontaneity and Larger than Life
personality but instead I want to take
this time to reflect on who uncle sea
truly was to us and laughter yet at the
same time he was calm and steady as a
gentle breeze his Spirit was the
brightest his heart was the purest and
his presence the kindest even in his
final days his warmth his peace and his
unwavering smile were
infectious above all the most inspiring
thing about Uncle sea was his faith no
matter what face he never doubted never
wavered never gave up and never cursed
God and because of that neither will we
we will carry his Spirit forward living
each day as he did with joy with
resilience and with an unshakable trust
in
God Uncle Sean I know you wouldd be
really proud to see me graduate from
Oakwood in in May and when I walk across
the stage I'll be thinking about you and
all the times you called me to check up
on me and see if Oakwood was still the
same same and if our daily bread was
still around the corner which I don't
think it is but we love you Uncle Sean
and you'll always be my funny
[Applause]
one U my name is tamarat I'm the uh the
best friend the uh as we used to joke
the other brother the uh not by Blood
but uh justice deep Sean will tell
you so I met Sean um
I met Sean 40 years over 40 years ago I
was nine he was about
eight and
uh
Ivor we refer to him as Al Ivor and I
were in fourth grade
together and uh we became Fast Friends
immediately um best
friends even at four even at fourth
grade um so
myself ivore and another buddy of ours
ahed uh decided to have a
sleepover and so um it was going to be
at my house so we were all excited me
ivvo ahed and um the day came and I
remember the door bell rang and
I ran to the door and uh my mom you know
greeted Mrs Meyers and Al and um Al got
one foot in the door and then I saw this
little person come behind him and slide
past him and dart past all of us and run
into my
house and I said who is
this I didn't know him I didn't I didn't
even know Al had a little
brother let alone that he was coming to
the house you know
um so it was then I realized that um
Ivor and sha were a package deal
okay
um and we had a blast that night you
know I remember one at one point it was
uh it was me Ivor and ahed and we were
in my room and I could hear in the
living room my mom say
tamarod your little friend Sean is
backflipping on the
couch you know and I and I went out
there my mom was sitting there watching
her shows and right next to her on the
couch Sean was just back flipping run
back up on the couch back flipping back
flipping and that that that kind of ex
that experience kind of sums up
sha
um fun full of
life um
free and uh with a
childish sense of wonderment that he
never lost right yeah you know if we
could all be so lucky to maintain that
quality I will
miss my
brother I love you Sean
[Applause]
okay hello everyone
um what I'm about to say I mean as the
deepest compliment that I know how to uh
give to Uncle
Shawn um Shawn left a very deep impact
on my life on my heart and on my
mind and
our our relationship obviously is my
uncle but there's also an
unspoken connection between me and Shan
spoken
unspoken and um when Shawn was going
through everything that he was going
through the family and
everything um during that time I
started running through some of the
emotions myself uh going through cancer
and things like that and you know
there's a lot of people in this world
that fold the moment anything bad
happens in their life like people always
think they have it worse than everyone
else and someone's always got it worse
than you and um when I saw what Uncle
Shawn was going through it started
bringing me back to some of those things
that I went through and guys I only went
through like a glimpse of what Uncle
Shawn went through the sleepless nights
in the hospital the heart racing where
you can't sleep the life-threatening
infections the bone marrow biopsies the
nausea the the list goes on and on and
cancer is it is um it is a battle that I
wouldn't wish on
anybody
and I started feeling some of that and
seeing him go through so much more that
I went through and it made me realize
that the
ultimate the
ultimate thing
that well I'm not exactly sure how to
say this and I didn't write this down
but as his body was
breaking as the world was crashing
around
him every single thing was failing but
yet his Spirit was never broken and that
is so much easier
said that is so much easier said than
done like people say that you see it in
the movies I like you everyone's seen a
lot of y'all probably seen Rocky right
and he's like it's not about how hard
you can hit but how hard you can get hit
and keep on going and the thing is
that all you guys just spoke about his
his Spirit how funny he was comical
lighthearted and he was was a light in
this world and the fact is when the
world was crashing around him he was
still that it's not like he changed his
character he he he remained the same man
and so he left an impact on my life and
I think um is an honor that he was is my
uncle and I'm proud to have known him
for you guys the family for him to be
your father for him to be your husband
brother
son Uncle everything dude it's it's an
honor to know to know this man and it's
one of the greatest marks you can leave
so I think if we can all take something
away um take the spirit the fight the
light everything that Sean brought to
this world and apply it to your life and
uh you'll live a life that will be well
remembered and impact that like look how
many people are here that's what you do
when you live a life like that guys so I
love you Uncle Sean and um it's an honor
[Applause]
my name is
to show that you
know this is the impact that
sean1 and we're well into 202
I never had schools
like and when I gotg
were
iny no that's fine that's fine what's up
people online how you doing okay all
right so as I was saying you know um hey
what was I
saying that's what happen when you get
old boy the Mind start to go Brooklyn
thank you thank you thank you thank you
he would always whenever I would talk to
him he would always like hey CLE yo you
remember that day that we took the drums
out and we went to Prospect Park and we
was just out there playing the drums and
just singing and whatnot and I'm like
yes Sean I remember you tell me every
time we talk the same story every time
you know but that's Sean you know what
I'm saying everybody kept saying how how
you know pure he was and that's exactly
what he is what he was he was pure
whenever I tell people about Sean I'm
like yo
this cat was the most pure person i' had
ever met I'm not a very religious person
you know but I remember in the
scriptures there was one guy that they
talked about somebody helped me out um
that was like real just faithful and
pure and just you
know Jesus hey it might have been Jesus
I don't know
look my look they know me you know what
I'm saying they know me so
I may not see Sean again but he knows
you know I'll be trying to do whatever I
can to to to to break in and so we can
holler at each other you know what I
mean but uh I don't think it was was it
David or somebody who's which one who
joob there you go yeah that's him that's
him that's if that's if that's if that's
if but Hey listen I don't know all the
names of all the people and all of that
but I do remember I was like okay that
Sean he was the most pure person I'd
ever know Sean was what 50 51
right 51 year old
man but whenever I looked at him and
thought of him I always saw a kid a
child you know and not in a
disrespectful manner but just that that
that that innocence that Purity you know
and that was him never changed and the
crazy part about it
is when I found out that he passed I
told my
mother and she remembered him
and I think she met him
once and she remembered him and then I
spoke to another friend of mine who we
went to liou together in
Brooklyn and I told him hey you know I
got to go out to the funeral and so on
he was like well who passor I said my
friend
Shawn and he remembered them I didn't
even know they
met he was like yeah the the the tall
guy right the Jamaican kid and I was
like yeah he passed oh my God I'm so
sorry I was like like you know
Sean but that's the impact that he had
you know you meet him once and you you
never forget him that's just the the
person that he was you know so we have
family here from all over the world you
know I came from Texas you have people
from California people from you know all
over that came here to to send our
farewells to Sean he had that much of an
impact on us okay uh
um yeah so to his
children I will
say you know you may have lost the
father but you gain a whole bunch of
uncles and
aunts a whole bunch of uncles and aunts
all
right that's my time man my my mind just
went blank so that means it's time for
me to get the headup off the stage thank
you about get
hey good morning everyone um I probably
have predated so many other people here
I have known Sean pretty much since I
was a child and I know his parents his
dad was in the Jamaican military with my
father um years and years
ago um perhaps the most popular verse in
the Bible or one of the most popular
verses in the Bible is that God so loves
the world that he gave and he gave and
he gave and he gave and I think you know
when you know Jesus or when you have H
have you have a relationship with him
it's your notion to
give
and my remembrance of Shan is you know
as a young adult those were some of the
most Salient memories was that you know
he was going
to have an impact on the world that he
was going to make sure that people knew
that there was something bigger than
life and that there was somebody who was
going to change the world not only for
him but for everybody else and I
remember you know him being kind to so
many people and if you have ever been to
the Myers home you know that it's always
inviting you know that it's always a
party and they have good parties and I
remember even at times you would have a
party people are drinking alcohol the
music is
playing and somehow sha and Al made it
their point to duty in the midst of the
music music hitting your soul to sit
down in that moment open the Bible and
to tell you about God and that this
really made more of a difference than
just sitting down
there and you know a lot of times people
would think that Al was kind of like his
mentor or you know the person he
followed behind but you'd always hear
that Echo if you want something go ask
Sean he's Kinder and he's sweeter and
he's more
loving and not to knock Alan
anyway um but that was the ongoing
sentiment and that there was there was
always that feeling of love and of
welcome when you interacted with
him and I can only just imagine you know
the experience that Auntie vadney Uncle
Ronnie all his brothers are experiencing
that
void um but I can and of course you know
over the years you know I've I've gotten
updates as to what's happening in his
life and you know the great things you
know him being you know a disciple of
God making a difference him having
children him having a wife and you know
you hear the stories oh he met the most
beautiful woman and they make such the
such a great Union so you hear the words
out there and you get to be an example
and he's an example of a father and I
can just imagine how challenging and how
heartbreaking it is um with everything
that's happening but I can tell you sha
may have loved all of you but definitely
he loved God more and every time that he
spoke about God he heard about God he
lit up and it made such a huge
difference in his life and I can only
just have some
assurance that God has given us him for
51 years and right now we give him back
to God for him to say welcome my good
and faithful service my good and
faithful servant you guys be
blessed good morning good morning just a
reminder that we will have Reflections
at near the end of the service at this
time we're going to have the musical
selection thank you so much
[Music]
I would love to tell you what I
think of
Jesus since I found in my friend so
strong and
[Music]
true I would tell you how he changed my
life
completely he did something that no
other
friend could
[Music]
do no one El
for For
Me Like
Jesus there's no other friend so
kind as
[Music]
she no one else could take the
sin and darkness from me
oh how much he
[Music]
car for
me
every day he comes to
me with new
Assurance more and more I understand his
words of
love but I'll never know just why he
came to
save
me till some day I
see his blessed
face up
above no one
never cared for
me quite like
Jesus there's no other friend so
kind as
[Music]
he no one else could take the
sin and darkness from me
oh how much he
cared for
[Music]
me oh how much he
car
for
[Music]
me for
[Laughter]
[Music]
this
one m
[Music]
soul will
put M
[Music]
me
b
[Music]
for son
in toee
[Music]
more
iness
one m
soul will
put
me
[Music]
be more
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm a tante Meyers Al ivor's wife and
Sean's
sister-in-law I met sha in November of
1997 in the middle of the
night he was so excited that Al was home
from college that he forgot to put on
his pajama
pants that's right I met him in his
boxers I thought this is a funny
guy the next morning while driving to
church he got out of the car at a
stoplight walked over to our car to tell
Al something
funny this was before cell phones kids
young
people when Sean walked away Al looked
at me and said he missed
me later that day we visited a local
hospital to bring encouragement and
prayer to the patients when sea started
praying I heard a familiar Passage
I opened my eyes it was Psalms chapter
91 I was in disbelief that he had
memorize the entire chapter that passage
that the nephews read that was Psalms 91
that's a long chapter and he had it by
memory I was so impressed that he would
pray the prayers of David as his
personal prayers to bless others in
later years these prayers were coined
David
prayers whenever I was going through
something difficult I would call sha and
say I need David
prayers he would pray for me like he was
personally going through it
himself he even extended the David
prayers for my friends that he barely
knew he would pray for them every day
for years when they found out that he
was that he was praying for them every
day it made an impact on their
life Shawn was a jokester but when it
came to prayer he was very
serious when he and I were both
diagnosed with autoimmune diseases we
bonded even
more learning how to take care of our
bodies we loved sharing healthy recipes
and health tips to improve our
health I take
pride in the fact that I could make Sean
laugh so hard until he would say taunt
stop my stomach
hurts and he would do it with that
crackle
laugh even throughout his journey with
cancer he would we would both crack a
laugh until it
hurt Sean taught me how to pray and
appreciate the small blessings in life
that most people would ignore he taught
me to give thanks to God for
everything he truly became a brother to
me he wasn't just Al Rowan and Tony's
brother he was mine
too I vow to you Veronica to always be
here for you when you need
me we will always be sisters nothing can
ever change
that Sarai Savannah
Judah you still have your beautiful
strong mother but you also have me and
all of your other aunties and
uncles I don't care what you need if for
some reason Mommy can't get it you call
me I love you like you are one of my
own remember you're not
alone Jesus and all of your family will
help you get through
this you will see your father again
be faithful to Jesus unto death like he
was and you will receive a Crown of Life
with him when Jesus comes I love
[Applause]
you yeah uh Sean was not just my little
baby brother but he was my
friend uh I remember when I came to
America
2009 got my first job Sean would take me
to work like every day pick me up at
night and never
[Music]
complain we do gardening together we do
so
much he even his last few weeks at the
hospital every chance I get I spend with
him and we just stay in that room and
watch cooking show even Alo he could not
eat
you know watch cooking
show and you know we just talk and he
never
complain even Al he was going through so
much pain you know and I know he's in a
better place
and he's a good man one in a
million and I know with Sean my life
will never be the
same that's all
[Applause]
tribute to my
brother-in-law from the moment I came to
America sha Meers my brother-in-law was
a mentor in my life we worked together
at his mother's group home and he always
was a family person being his company
was always a pleasure he always touched
someone lives with kindness care and
loving and peaceful nature these special
memories of him will always bring a
smelling be in my heart if only I could
have you back Sean for just a little
while then we could just sit and talk
again just like we used to do you're
always in my heart until we meet
again that's it
so
um there the
theme to sha
Myers
um and you'll notice that everybody keep
talking about
him the same Sean was a very transparent
person
um I could talk about Sean for the rest
of the day but they put me on the limit
so I to write down my
thoughts
um so I'm the
second of our parents four
boys and I'll be telling you
about the man I had the pleasure and
honor of calling a
brother and a
friend speaking specifically about his
his sense of
humor and his
passion I've overheard or wives
or kids the nephews the nieces drawing
comparisons between us the four boys um
as being social and and funny um and
they've all come back to the same
conclusion Sean is the
funniest and we never disputed it cuz he
he actually
was um I can recall growing up in
Freeport New York there were countless
occasions when sea would have get in
trouble
and Alan I would look on in
amazement at that the height of her
mom's
anger
Shan
would okay so at the height of um Sean
would Alan I would look on in amazement
at the height of Mom's anger he would
say something funny
and mom would say
Sean and then her whole facial
expression would change as she starts
laughing turn around and walk
away blurting out
cha now if you Google
cha it says cha is a Jamaican word that
can be used as an exclamation of
annoyance
um Alan and I never got those
breaks we got whatever was coming to us
in concentrated
form with salt and
lemon while
Sean Sean got milk and
honey let me let me let me let me
correct
it organic soy milk and Hy
there was nothing that Sean could do
that would make you dislike him in
retrospect I think it's
because as you've heard other people say
you
um you felt him
um you felt him as an individual and
knew he had a pure heart and the best of
intentions this coupled with a sense of
humor and as that infectious SM
infectious
laugh when he laughed you laughed and
you didn't even have to hear the
joke when you as a
dad can make your own teenage daughters
laugh and your seven-year-old son laugh
at will you got skills
sha loved people from all
demographics age socioeconomic status
religion and could easily start a
conversation with anyone anywhere
anytime and the person would walk away
feeling like they just made a best
friend as for his
passion and you've heard
this Sean was passionate about Kung Fu
specifically Wing Chong they Alan and
Sean um uh practice for hours each day
now somehow they always ended up getting
a fight every
day like 365 days a year it's sometimes
twice um as a big brother who was more
mature and took my big brotherly role
very seriously I never stopped a
fight I ensured that the fights occurred
in a well-rolled
environment
where
um where no damage could occur to a
parents
home these fights typically started in
the house and I would interrupt in mid
kick or them out the house where they
would proceed and yes Shan always came
in
second but I never understood why
because he was clearly a better
fighter it could have been
psychological perhaps Al wouldn't allow
him to wouldn't allow himself to lose to
Shawn because Shawn was his baby brother
or perhaps it was because Shawn was
smaller and it was harder to hurt Al the
point here though is that Sean's
passionate about standing up for what he
felt was right regardless of what the
outcome would be he never backed down
unlike most people from the planet Earth
that may have one
passion Sean was passionate about
everything he did he was passionate
about his diet he was passionate about
working out he was passionate about
praying I think he did this three times
a day and every time you got in a car
with Sean we're going to pray before we
even start the car he was passionate
about feeding his God's
sheep he was passionate about his
sermons if he's in a conversation with
you and you said something that he could
use in a sermon he got immediately
excited and told you on the spot that he
was going to use that in a
sermon he was committed to journaling
his daily experiences I think he did
this for over 25 years I asked him one
once if he ever missed a day and he said
occasionally but he would catch it up
the next day I asked him why journaling
and he said so that he doesn't forget
his blessings and all the Lord has done
for him and brought him
through he said after a while we often
forget the small and large Miracles that
occur in the past and he doesn't want to
forget he also said that in so doing
when new challenges arrive in your life
you can look back and see what the Lord
has brought you through and in so doing
have greater faith that he will once
again bring you
through with all the passions Sean had
he was most passionate about striving
for the
kingdom I can't count the amount of
times we've been in conversations and he
would say man Rowan I can't wait for God
to
come we won't have
to you know we won't have to put up with
this we won't have to put up with that
but in my mind I'm thinking well
actually he who who has begun a good
work in me is still working on a Sean um
Sean was passionate about so many things
that
he he actually had them prioritized and
at the top of his list he was most
passionate about striving for the
kingdom he walked the walk and talked
the talk with
humility his life and his his death will
forever be a powerful example to me and
my
family of how a true Christian should
live in this day in this
age Shawn finished his race and his
crown is
sure he may have been the youngest of us
four but now it seems like he's the
wisest my goal is to see him again and I
feel like his life was a practice how to
walk with Christ manuscript and my
intention is to use it for the remainder
of my days amen may God continue to have
mercy upon us and our family and heal
the voids in our hearts thank
you so I can't top that so I'm gonna say
just a few
words so when I married this guy right
here I married a whole
family and um I didn't gain a
brother-in-law
I gained a
brother Shawn was my spiritual mentor
and he too taught me how to pray he
taught me how to pray as a wife because
that's the first time I went to Shawn as
a
wife Sean was my spiritual sound
sounding
board and I was Stacy cat
sha is always there for you and every
way I don't need to repeat anything that
anyone's already said but I want to
share one special moment that stood
out when I was pregnant with Madison my
first
born his MADD
goo M got stuck at
work and I was going to L's class by
myself and I called Sean and I said Sean
row can't make it down I'm at Mary
Washington I don't want to do L mods by
myself he's like I got you Stacy
cat Sean came to the MOX class with
me I have a lot of memories Sean used to
call me at work Stacy cat what you doing
I'm at work
Sean all right just a moment you got a
moment I'm like yes Sean and he'd asked
me some of the craziest
questions and Sean like you said before
you can never be mad at Sean under no
circumstances I'm going to miss my
brother so I'm not saying
goodbye I'm saying I'll see you later
Sean I'm going to be here and I always
have been for my mother-in-law I love
her like my mother for my sister in-law
she's my sister and my three children
you know Auntie Stacy's here I got you
and I love you and I love you Mom
[Applause]
[Music]
ah good afternoon
everyone
um when I was growing up as a child I
always thought to myself I would never
have
children and I would never get married
because those were my thoughts because I
said how do you have children what if
something happens to them what if they
die how do you go and how do you
live well what I what was a thought or
what were my
thoughts they became a reality
on January 5th at 1:13
p.m. holding my son Sean holding his AR
his
hand and saying
goodbye so him took his last
breath this is something I never thought
I would ever because TR Sean's illness
for some reason I thought Sean was going
to be
well just that Mom just willing him to
be well but God saw
it God was ready for Sean God lent him
to to us for 51 years 51 beautiful years
we worked not only as mom and son but we
worked together from 2009 until the 4th
of March he was diagnosed with cancer on
the 7th of March his last day at work
was on the 4th of
March and our lives have
changed
but life goes on I can see this is Shan
this is what Sean would have loved just
seeing you all seeing all his friends
from
kindergarten to now it tells who Sean
was and I know he lives on in my I can
never I don't know how I will go on but
I know we have
to Sean has been my everything they'll
sometimes they say oh you're a husband
and wife because we when we fast he
works for me we work and I said John you
didn't do this okay maam but he's not
foring he's not he's such a peacemaker
has always been this
Peacemaker and um now we just have
to there are days when I'm home now and
I just think Sean is going to walk in or
he's going to be outside he loves go he
loved gardening and he has a raised bed
outside and he's watering his plant and
mom come look at this we have some new
Tomatoes I said Sean I just thought Mom
we have some new Tomatoes he planted two
trees in our backyard two pairs and
every day a new one came out and he
would call me Mommy you have to come see
this and this was who Sean was just love
the simple things of life and just love
life I watched him last August on a t on
a video that I had I did it cuz he was
watering the plants and he said said
this is how you fight cancer and he's
watering and he has the water shooting
up in the air and he says this is how
you fight cancer with God's
help amen and that's Sean we're walking
out Sean never let us leave that house
unless he comes to the car and prays he
has to pray before he prays for his
children in the mornings before they go
after school in the nights before
anybody comes to the house and they are
going Sean comes by the car and he says
a prayer and that's who Sean was and
again this is a reflection just look at
this that's what Sean would have loved
this and guys I just want to say thank
you thank you you will always be a part
of her life Sean is not
here but you will always each every one
of you here today you're here because
you love Sean and I know that I feel the
love and we feel the love and I just
want to say thank you thank you to
everyone before I go I just want to add
this little Sean was about s 18 left
finished they were in Brooklyn bogy
man's days but sea didn't have two
nickel to rub together Shawn called me
one day met some little girl Sea called
me mommy I'm getting married so I said
okay he he said on the phone he said
mommy did you just hear what I said I
said yeah I heard you he said Mommy I'm
getting married and I said okay so he
said okay mommy later I heard he told
the person we're not getting married
Mommy I didn't like how mommy sound so
we're not because he he was still a kid
didn't have $2 but that's who sha is
full of sea is was filled with humor and
again I just want to say thanks to
everyone for your support and for being
here for us Sean would have loved this
and I know that I am striving to be
because I was with Shan the minute he
died and up to the minute Shan his face
was just
radiant his skin was bronze and I saw
the peace and we all felt it our pastor
from our church was there and he saw
Shawn and he said he spoke it on it at
church the following week he said just
seeing Shan it was amazing Shan knew on
the 26th of
December sorry yeah the 26th of December
they called us into a room and they said
Sean is terminal and he has weeks to
live and everybody were crying all of us
were crying I went behind him and I
hugged him and I held him because I
couldn't let him see the tears and sha
just sat there with this
peace everyone Stacy Rowan tante Al all
of us and Sean was just looking as
looking at us with such a peace so I
know that Sean
is when sea wakes up on that great G up
morning I know whose face sha would be
looking in the eyes of God the face of
Jesus and I am striving to be there
because I want to see my son again I
want to hold him again I want to just
Embrace him again so pray for the family
and thank you again
[Applause]
everyone
um my dad uh was my best friend and
um we had a lot in common um and I
remember when I found out that he was
terminal and that
he
would um that he might pass I was very
scared um my family knows this but um
when I was 12 I got diagnosed with
depression and anxiety um and over time
it's come in waves
but
um when I came to the reality that this
was going to happen and that my dad was
going to pass I was very devastated
because I didn't know how I would go
through it and I didn't know how I would
be okay because he was such a big part
of why I was okay and why I was able to
enjoy
life
um
and I remember the first day he passed I
tried
replaying all the memories that I had of
all the sermons my dad taught me um he
would share at at least one quick quick
sermon with us um every day even if it
was 11:00 p.m. at night he would have us
get out of our beds on a school night to
make sure that we had at least 30
minutes of a devotional that he would
come up with um every single
day
um anyways I I knew that I had to find
an
answer um um because I didn't know how I
was going to get through it and I
remembered one specific thing um my dad
always taught us
he um said that you have a physical body
but you also have a spiritual body and
you know in order to live in your
physical body you need to feed it um and
that's how you survive in
order to survive spiritually and not
give up you need to ask God for help and
for spiritual food and at first you know
I didn't understand what that meant and
my dad explained it to me and he said
um spiritual food would be prayer um
reading the Bible and just yearning for
the Lord
um and I didn't understand it I
understood it but I guess not in the way
that he did um until now
because that's the only way I've been
surviving is asking God every day for
food um to to feed my spiritual body and
keep it going keep it moving
um so that I can't so that I don't give
up because there were many times before
where I wanted to give up and you know
my dad kept encouraging me all the time
my whole family has been so supportive
um but I don't think that I realized how
important it is to
Value all the little moments and um
everything beautiful in life
until I realized how my dad did that and
how he was able to do it even when he
was
literally about to pass and
um I remember just looking at him every
day for that whole time he was sick I
mean since he first got diagnosed and I
was
just I was so I didn't know how he he
was okay like he was just he every time
I asked him if he was okay he would
smile and just thumbs up he couldn't
talk because he had a tria but every
time I asked him he never not once said
that he was in pain or
uncomfortable
and
um I believe that even though what he
went through was hard and terrible that
God gave him a sense of Peace um and
that's why he was able to get through it
even though he ended up passing I still
think I still know that he won the war
against the devil and he always talked
about how life was a
war
um and a fight between you and the
devil and now I know
that since my dad was able to beat him I
need to beat him too
and I can't let him I can't let the
devil ruin
everything that my dad fought
for um thank you all for being
here
um my dad my dad valued all of you so
much I mean he would talk he would talk
I'm sorry I'm rambling but he would talk
to me all the time about like every
story that was told up here I've been
told from my dad firsthand he he loves
everybody and all his friends and um he
loved talking about you guys all the
time to me and my sister and he had so
many stories um but yeah he really
enjoyed life and cherished it and now I
cherish it more than I have ever
so um thank
[Applause]
[Music]
you hello yes Judah can you share uh
with us something about daddy
daddy was a good dad and he bring me
the daddy was a good dad and he bring me
the fun
[Applause]
a okay I just want to start by saying um
thank you for joining our family during
this very difficult time um thank you to
our
family and our friends who have been so
supportive from the very
start um you
have provided um comfort love um
financial support and for that I'm so
grateful I also want to say thank you to
Nova Korean
Church um
thank you for your support as
well your
prayers uh the the fredburg SDA church
for the meals that you all have
delivered to our homes the flowers the
prayers the support I'm so
grateful um I also want to thank Dr
Reynolds and uh for her support she was
a naturopath doctor that helped Sean
throughout his um cancer Journey
the medical staff that were also um a
blessing and I also want to thank um the
GoFundMe supporters um we um asked for
financial help um to help pay for um the
naturopath doctor that worked with Sean
and also to go to a place in Mexico
called hope for cancer and I just want
to say
how touched we were by the financial
support that we got so that Sean can do
uh go get that treatment um those people
that we've never met that donated you
know large amount of money small amount
of
money it we were so so uh touched by um
your kindness towards us and I want to
thank
you um
I also want to um read um a letter that
I wrote on my thoughts about sha and
uh it's uh it says Dear sha I can't
believe that you're no longer with us it
feels like a dream you were the
strongest person I
knew and so special to me I love your
true love and Devotion to the Lord you
were the real deal
you are serious about God and His word
yet so funny and silly since we met
you've always been a down toe guy so
easy to talk to and so humble and kind
you were the fun parent who didn't mind
driving to the nearby gas station with
the kids to get them a late night snack
on the weekend you were the healthiest
person I knew your discipline was
sometimes annoying but very admirable
like always food labels or asking the
server many questions about your
order when you were diagnosed with
cancer I rarely saw you cry and you
never once complained to me or asked why
when asked how you were feeling you
always raised your thumb to say you were
okay even at times when I knew you were
not your peace and strength were
Supernatural and I knew it came from
Jesus I don't understand understand the
why but I'm thankful for our 20 years
together God was and is good to us we
live through many challenges but we also
experience beautiful amazing moments
thank you for your love to our children
and me and for being the priest of our
home you ran your race your crown is
ready I pray we live our lives living
with the love and kindness you taught us
for now I won't say goodbye but good
night because we will soon meet again on
Resurrection
morning we will meet
again when the Lord Jesus returns and
the dead in Christ will resurrect
first what a day marvelous day that will
be and for now now good night my love
good
night I also want to thank um the living
Mana prayer team
who started praying for Sean the moment
that he was diagnosed with cancer um
they we would pray for Sean every day
twice a
day and and they were faithful and
committed and I just want to let them
know that their support and their
commitment was so amazing and so
special it carried us gave us strength
it sustained us it preserved US during
that very difficult time even now and
for that I thank you we love you and um
we will like I said we will meet him
again let's stay let's stay faithful so
that we can do that thank you
[Music]
um this song that we are about to sing
is called goodness of
God
and there's something already really
special about this
song but
we played this song in the
last maybe 20 minutes before he passed
away
[Music]
and there was just a really special
moment in the room while this song
played and he seemed extra at peace
so
um everyone should be at peace right now
too and think about the memories with
Uncle sh
[Music]
I love you
Lord for your mercy never fails
me all my
days I've been held in your hand
from the moment that I wake
up until I lay my
head oh I will
sing of the
goodness of
God cuz all my life you have been
faithful cuz all my life you have been
so so
[Music]
good with every breath that I am
a oh I will
sing of the
goodness of
God I love your
voice you have me through the
fire in Darkest Night
you are close like no
other I've known you as a
father I've known you as a
friend and I have lived in the
goodness of
God cuz all my life you have been
faithful
[Music]
cuz all my life you have been so so
good with every breath that I am
aable oh I will
sing of the goodness of
God your goodness is running after it's
running after me
your goodness is running after it's
running after me when my life laid down
I Surrender now I give you
everything your goodness is running
after it's running after
me your goodness is running after it's
running after
running after me when my life laid down
let surrender now I give you
everything your goodness is running
after it's running after
[Music]
me sing with us
family cuz all my life you have been
cuz all my life cuz all my life you have
been so so
good with every breath that I am
a oh I will sing of the
goodness of
God oh I will sing of the goodness of
God oh I will
sing of the
goodness of God
[Applause]
[Music]
for
sure
[Music]
this
okay okay
[Music]
Heavenly
Father this moment is
here Lord I've asked you to strengthen
me
please
Lord speak through
me I pray it in Jesus name
amen I'm
here a few months ago um
I did a
funeral and
uh I just kept thinking in my mind
this I'm not doing this for my brother
he's going to
live so
um to be here right now doing this is uh
surreal
and
uh I know there are a lot of
wies and when Sean passed I started
asking the question
why and the Lord spoke to me and has
been speaking to me
and so I want to talk to you today about
the
why uh Psalms 116 and verse1
15 the Bible says
precious in the sight of the Lord is the
death of his
Saints that's a very strange
verse precious
in the sight of the Lord is the death of
his Saints why is it
precious why is
it
valuable why is it expensive why is it
costly why is it worth much to God the
death of his Saints what does he use it
for that's the question I want to answer
today so when my brother and I were
growing up up when we came from
Jamaica and came to the
states um one of the things that we did
every day was we played Batman and
Robin every
day every single day I was
Batman and he was
Robin and if you ever watched Batman and
Robin it was always like a cliffhanger
at the end of every episode Batman and
Robin were gonna die for sure this time
but you had to stay tuned for the next
time and and Batman was always saving
Robin and that was me and Sean every
day we were born 10 months
apart um but we were like
twins we came to the states we got on
the break dancing together we got into
the martial arts
together and by the way while we would
fight I would make sure that I never hit
my brother
especially in the
face so I'd let him do his thing then
I'd show him who the boss
was but I always cared for him that I
would never hurt my brother and I never
did we got the same best
friend we went to colleges close to each
other we had the same group of
friends
X-Men Sean Penny cook Mark small back in
uh Freeport uh ahed
tamrad we had the whole we did
everything together we got into the
music together we were baptized together
as
Baptists and then years later we would
be baptized together on the same day as
seventh day Adventists
we were in the music industry together
we were dancers together then rappers
together we decided to walk away from
Fame together I remember the day that I
went to Sean I was like Sean I got to
tell you something I'm walking away from
the group and he was like I came to the
same conclusion
myself we walked away from the music
together we ended up going to the same
Adventist College together we both
married California
Girls we both became
Pastors in September of
2023 I had
this overwhelming sense of depression I
don't know where it came from I had no
idea what was going on with me I thought
I was I thought I was just losing my
mind this Spirit of
depression came over me it was
unexplainable and it would not
leave and I remember that as a result of
this I ended up writing something
because I just been thinking about death
and and what heaven's going to be like
in the reality of Heaven because the
world just got so dark to
me and I ended up
writing this story called Heaven's
diary and there was a a a story of a man
who was coming up in the resurrect
resurrection of Christ and he's
chronicling he's he's journaling his
journey from the grave to the kingdom of
heaven at the second coming of
Jesus and I remember after writing it it
took me seven days to write it and put
it to music and after writing it I
started sending it out to people my
Ministry my family and people who
listened to it were like blown away this
is amazing how did you write this and I
would tell them I don't know it just
kind of came over me because I just had
this sense of just like what is this
world if there is no
Heaven one of the last discussions my
brother and I had before his voice
started going was about Heaven's diary
he listened to it and he and I were
talking about how Heaven is going to be
such an awesome place and the things
that we're going to do there things that
people don't even think about and that
is as his voice was going
the journal began with these words awake
awake he's hearing the voice of the Son
of God and he says the last thing he
remembered was him being surrounded by
his family as he was slipping into death
and now he's hearing the voice of
God on March 8th SE was diagnosed with
cancer March 7th he was diagnosed with
cancer and and I remember thinking to
myself not
Sean we have a huge family huge sha is
the king of Health in our
family nobody took care of their health
more than my brothers so not
Shawn a and if Shawn does have cancer
then if anyone's going to beat it it's
going to be
him it's going to be him
because Lord that would be too crazy to
have cancer fall on the person who says
I'm going to take care of my body and
live to the glory of God that would that
would
be and so when he was diagnosed with
this I want you to understand that that
Batman kicked
in when sha was in 11th grade
12th grade and I was in my first year of
college and Sean called me up Mom and
Dad were up in New York and Sean called
me and told me that some guys came to
the
house trying to fight him and it was the
only time Sean ever made a call to me
like
that so I got off the
phone got on the phone my best friend
tamarat I was like T
we have
beef he said what's going on I said I
need you to get everybody I need you to
get everybody you
can T's at Virginia Union I'm at
Virginia state and in a matter of an
hour there are five
carloads five carloads of us
driving down to fredicksburg Virginia my
parents aren't home my father collects
guns
we emptied the house of the
guns every
car praise
God that God we're here today that means
everything turned out all right so don't
even go further to well what happened
we're here today nobody's in
jail we're
here but that was a kind of protection
that I had for my
brother and so becoming a Christian now
that's kicked in for the glory of
God so now I'm like Sean okay we're
going to fight this we are going to pull
out every weapon against cancer that we
can we're going to fight this Sean
I got together a prayer
team we're going to we're going to pray
spe everything that Sean's going through
every treatment that he has we're going
to be praying that that if his blood
count needs to be this we need to know
everything that's going on with Sean and
we're going to pray for a miracle
because my brother will be
healed and I didn't realize that I had
been watching a miracle until after my
brother
died
when they told sea that he had
cancer and that they had to do surgery
immediately and they had to put a tra
into his throat and they were going to
have to put a feeding bag into him
because he wouldn't be able to eat
anymore and his voice may not return and
they had stage four esophagal can
esophagal
cancer and then to put him in a surgery
that
day I was in
Alabama and I remember when he was going
into the surgery and I thought to myself
how is this possible how was my
brother's life about to change so
dramatically in one day in one day he
goes from everything is fine it's just
strep throat to you have cancer you may
not be able to talk again you will not
be able to eat again and all that could
come to my mind was job
and I remember in a
sense that that diagnosis to my brother
was like that D it was like they were
diagnosing
me and when they did the
surgery then I FaceTime my brother after
and I was expect I don't know what I was
expecting to see but what I saw I was
not expecting to
see because beyond the tra beyond the
feeding
to my
brother sees me on FaceTime and he does
this Sean how you doing
I don't know about you but to have a
voice for 50 years and then suddenly be
told you may never speak
again to love eating and and cooking and
to be told that you will not be able to
taste to be Erica Meyer's
son and be told that you will not be
able to experience her cooking
and I looked at my brother and I thought
to myself okay he's in shock right
now but when he wears off I'm going to
be there for him
because th this is not this can't be
happening to my
brother and he's going to be overwhelmed
pretty soon and so I watched him that
day and I was just amazed I was
just and I said he's shock but it it'll
wear
off and we began going to
work everything that we could
do everything that we could
do
supplements
herbs looking into natural remedies
every day for 10
months our whole family we were
researching we were doing everything we
possibly could
and I have to tell you that it feels
like everything that could possibly go
wrong everything that could possibly go
wrong just when we thought okay we're
we're we're hitting the turn here it's
about to get better oh he got an
infection and because of the infection
because the way they put the tube in
this happened and now that set him back
and I remember watching my
brother through this entire
trial and I began to think to myself
he's
Batman how is he batmanning right
now how is he doing this right now now
you know he and I we're listen when when
we became Christians y y when we became
Adventists you all
know I think everybody was afraid to be
around us
because y'all heard why every one of
y'all needed to be Adventist you
remember that family you remember that
none of you
escaped nobody when y'all saw us coming
y'all were like all right time to
go because if if we don't escape now
they going and this was me and Sean for
everybody
friends family uncle aunt it didn't
matter who you
were you knew we were coming for you
what
we what we found that led us to walk
away
from
Fame and
money from the bottom of our hearts we
wanted it wasn't just to okay I know
this now I'm
good we wanted everybody to know what we
had learned we wanted every everybody to
know and experience the joy that we had
had and so Sean and I you know we we
grew in this and we walked in this and
and here's the thing you guys like y'all
know that out of you know with me and
sea my Ministry went public so people
knew me as the public speaker and Sean
was just you know in his Corner doing
his
thing and and people were like oh Pastor
Myers your sermon about the blueprint
and your sermon about this and and I saw
this on YouTube and that on YouTube and
I began to realize as I was watching my
brother that my brother was preaching a
sermon greater than anything I have ever
that has ever come out of my
mouth as I watched
Sean
live this
thing in the midst of a
trial I promise you
that I began to question my own
Christianity I mean maybe Sean did it
too because he and I talked and and Ron
and Tony we would always talk about man
you know this person died and that
person died a man what must that be like
and and I think in some
way God God gives his Saints a
supernatural thing I don't know how to
explain
it the Bible tells us to consider the
ant consider the
ant how it
gathers in the Harvest so that when
winter rolls around it's not found
wanting and what I want you to
understand everyone is that my my
brother my brother even though he walked
away from money he was
rich he was he had money in the
bank please understand what I mean when
I say he had money in the back I'm
talking about faith
money he had Faith dollars he was a
billionaire a and the reason why he was
such is because he learned the art of
investing
he bought while it was
low my brother invested while the cost
of Faith was low and so it's funny
because we were looking at his phone the
other day and we Sean has videos on his
phone he didn't release them to anybody
it's just videos of him picking up his
phone and doing stuff like
this all right
God it's time again and then you see him
look at the phone and then you see him
open the gate to his backyard and he
walks into the gate and he's like let's
do this and the video
ends
Sean what were you doing with
God and what did it have to do with the
backyard like help me
nobody knew he was doing these videos so
on his phone he' be sitting in his car
and uh what was the
song the goodness of God it's PL and
he's just in the car and he's looking at
the phone and he's crying and he's
pointing
up and he looks at the phone and the
video
stops those intimate moments with God
he was he was becoming rich so that he
had money when an emergency he had
enough funds for that rainy
day when the crisis hit my brother had
enough in his wallet to handle
it he was rich in faith and I thought to
myself how many of us do not realize
that we are we that we are poor
that we might talk about God and and say
we love God but but if you were faced
with a job like
situation would you have enough money in
the bank to handle the tribe the way you
had the way God wants you to handle it
and I watch you guys as my brother would
struggle to breathe mucus coming out of
his trick as he's struggling to breathe
and I'm like Sean and in my mind I'm
just like
I'm going to go crazy for my
brother I cannot watch this I cannot see
this Lord this is my little brother Lord
let's do
something and every time I ask my
brother Sean how you
doing Sean how you feeling better with
his whisper better
and I'm like Sean how how are
you doing
this
precious in the sight of the Lord is the
death of his
Saints not everybody dies well
not everybody who claims to be a
follower of the Lord walks into the
valley of the shadow of death fearing no
evil so when it happens
precious I want you to look at this
now see in my mind it's the job story so
you know we don't mind the job story
because in the job story job
lives and he gets a double portion at
the end of his oh hey give me a job
story if I can get the double portion
yeah so we want the job story but we
forget how often we forget that there's
a Jesus story
too that Jesus actually had to
die he actually went into the grave and
so in my mind I'm like all right Lord
this is a job story we're going to see
Shawn through up until Shawn's last
breath in my mind I'm like n the Lord
watch this the Lord's about to pull
something through watch
this and so when my brother took his
last breath y'all need to
understand
how the question why and I know I'm a
pastor I know Pastor you're you're the
Christian I know I know the verses you
know the trumpet was sound I know all of
that but I have to tell
you Lord help me to understand this
help me to understand
this you know what people going to say
they're going to say oh the H living
healthy what difference does that make
look at Shawn serving God what
difference look at Shawn look at
Shawn they're going to say look at
Sean that's why I shouldn't follow God
that's why it doesn't matter how I
live and the Lord said no
they're going to say look at
Shawn look at
Shawn look at how he lived his
life look at how he faced what every one
of us is going to
face look at how he smiled day by day
look at how when he was told you're
terminal everybody in the room including
the doctor is crying and sea is there
like
I didn't realize it then but the miracle
that we had been praying for was
happening before my
eyes I feel like my brother is that
character in the
bible let me say it this way
in my brother I feel like I met an
actual Bible
character like someone whose
story I began to understand that that
okay Lord you allow this to happen like
just as the devil came to Jo to God and
said I know job is your servant but I
bet you that if I this this this this
and this that he will curse you to your
face and all I can say is that God
trusted my brother
enough to allow the guy that is the
healthiest person in the
family who doesn't drink who doesn't
smoke who lives his I'm going God
trusted him enough to use his life as a
demonstration
what if Jesus
lived 10 more years father wouldn't his
life wouldn't he have been able to
accomplish
more
no in Jesus's
death he would save more than he did
when he was
alive oh so so
the death of Jesus was precious because
through his death other people came to
the
Lord that's why it's
precious that's why it's costly that's
why God can say all right life completed
now look at that
life look at how he lived his
life so in the song
strange my brother in the chorus quotes
Psalm 1 y'all probably heard it blessed
is the man that walketh not in the
counsel of
the chanting
it blessed is the
man that walketh not in the
counsel of the ungodly nor stth in the
way of Sinners nor sth in the seat of
the scornful but his Delight is in the
law of the Lord and in his law law does
he meditate day and night and then this
verse he shall be like a tree planted by
the rivers of waters that bringeth forth
his fruit in his season his Leaf shall
also not wither and whatsoever he doeth
shall prosper you know I've read this
verse a thousand times and it was not
until it was not until I Was preparing
this
message that I realized something
a
tree comes from a seed that has been
planted in the
earth I've always thought this verse was
talking about how a person lives their
life and and as they're living their
life their fruit will prosper but you
got to understand that a tree in order
for a tree to to grow something must
first go into the
ground and beloved this is when it hit
me
my brother's
life is like a
seed planted into the
ground that is going to bring forth
fruit to the glory of
God I did a tribute to my brother on
YouTube and then I connected Heaven's
diary with it because when he was dying
one of the last things he listened to
the day before he died died I said Sean
you want to listen to Heaven's diary and
he was like
yeah and as he as we he put I put it on
and it was playing and the whole family
was around and the words awake
awake and then the person saying the
last thing I remembered was being
surrounded by my loved ones it is then
that it hit me it is then that I
remembered it is then that I thought to
myself Lord tell me that I wasn't
writing this for my brother
how are we in a hospital room right now
with my brother dying and we're
surrounding him and he's listening to
this how is Lord were you was your hand
in this were you preparing us for this
months a year earlier before it
happened and as my brother is listening
to to to the to the part where where
they're ascending into heaven and he
starts doing this with his hands
if y'all have seen the video he starts
doing this and I'm there on the bed with
him and and we start doing this together
and I'm thinking to
myself
Sean I said
Lord give me a double portion of the
spirit that my brother
has give me a double portion of that
spirit let me tell
you thousands of people have listened to
that heaven's
diary and if that's thousands of seeds
that have been
planted to the glory of God because of
Sha's
death if there are people in here right
now who as a result of this moment will
walk away and say you know what I wasn't
considering God before I wasn't
considering Jesus before but now I might
consider
him if in the Kingdom of
Heaven There are those of you who are in
here today who will say
Sean do you
remember when you were telling me about
the Lord and I was
like the way you
died the way you
died that was the
seed that started me on my journey to
God I'm going tell you something in that
Resurrection morning when Jesus comes
the Bible says Jesus is going to come
and all who are asleep in the grave will
be resurrected so that we enter Heaven
at the same time together like a family
reunion if sea hears
that you are here because of his death
he's going to be like
no you you
serious come on
Jesus that's what he's going to
do you know it that's what he's going to
do because my brother was that type of a
guy he made you feel like you were the
the best at whatever it is you were
doing he made you feel like you were the
I would come to fredicksburg and and go
with Shawn to the gym and Shawn would
introduce me to people in the gym like
this is his best friend a meet so and so
and I'm just looking at this guy like
okay hi and Sean is acting like he is
his best
friend and the pride he had in in in in
in in having me meet his friend and then
having his friend meet his older brother
this is my older brother
Al let me tell you there is nothing
Shawn would love more than to be like
Jesus Remember the cousin I pray I was
praying to you about remember the Auntie
the uncle the friend this this is him
this is her
precious in the sight of the
Lord is the
death of his
Saints Lord why wouldn't you let my
brother
live he has so much more to do he's got
a family Lord why wouldn't you let him
live
and the Lord says through his
death many more will be
saved I have a statement I want to read
and then I'll
close one of my friends sent this to
me it's just a paragraph here's what it
says patience as well as courage has its
victories by meekness under
trial no less than by boldness in
Enterprise Souls may be one to
Christ the Christian who manifests
patience and cheerfulness under
bereavement and suffering who meets even
death itself with the peace and calmness
of an unwavering Faith May accomplish
for the gospel more than than he could
have affected by a long life of faithful
labor often when the servant of God is
withdrawn from active duty the
mysterious Providence which our
shortsighted vision would
lament is designed by God to accomplish
a work that otherwise would never have
been
done my brother showed us how to die
right he not only showed us how to
live he showed us how to die
right when we started keeping the
Sabbath we had understood that the
Sabbath was all about rest taking that
day to rest and and God was teaching us
how to rest and how to rest under
circumstances and rest under trial and
every seven day was like a drill okay
now I know you got all these things
going on but I want you to take this
time to
rest and seeing my brother
rest all the way through this
trial I would ask his kids guys did you
see your father cry cuz I know never saw
him cry did
you y'all never just walk by the living
room and just caught
them you know it's
real when in your own
house with your own
children with your own spouse where
where you let your hair down so to
speak you know it's
real when
even among the
closest of your
companions they can say
truly this was a child of
God so I'm closing with an
[Music]
appeal because Shan would want me
to he's sleeping now Resurrection
morning is coming
but he's going to ask
me Al what did you do at my
funeral and you I'm going to be like
Sean come
on the week before he
died no three days before he died we had
been out here for two weeks we went back
to Alabama because we thought everything
was Sean was on the up and up when we
landed we got the call that we had to
come back because he only had a few days
and when I heard that I FaceTime my
brother I was in my daughter's our
daughter's apartment when we got that
word and I FaceTime Rowan cuz he was
there at the hospital and he was in the
room with
Shawn Shawn was sleeping when I faced
time I was
crying I was stunned I was in shock I
was crying I I lost it and my brother
woke up and he saw me
crying and then he looked at me like
this in the midst of my Tears he looked
at me and he was like ow what are you
doing and I was like Sean Sean I'm sorry
I'm sorry all right
I'm
good that's the kind of
[Music]
Faith every time I think of my brother's
suffering the cancer has gone to his
liver the cancer has gone to his lungs
necrom Matic pneumonia who gets that in
their last days your lungs are now being
eaten from the
inside you can't breathe you can't talk
you can't walk the cancer is in your
bones everything in his body is broken
except his spirit
the sermon my brother
preached is greater than anything that
has ever come out of my
mouth and I have to say Lord search
me search
me give me a double portion of that
spirit
[Music]
if there is anyone here
today I'm not going to ask you to stand
up I'm not going to ask you to raise
your hand but I'm making this
appeal Sean wants to see you in the
Kingdom of
Heaven he's going to ask me Al what did
did you and I'm going say yes Sean I
did I told them I invited them
the way Sean's death would not be in
vain is when people hear how he died and
see his life that they'll be like you
know what yeah I'm willing to walk away
I'm willing to walk away from my million
dollars whatever that is I'm willing to
walk away from my fame from my glory I'm
willing to do that because the example
that I've seen in this man has changed
change my life so if there's anyone here
today who will even entertain the
thought of coming to follow Jesus I pray
that you will do
[Music]
that I pray that a seed will be planted
today in your
heart that will find its
fulfillment in us being together at that
great family
reunion that is only possible because of
the blood of
Jesus let's not make his death be in
vain I appeal to
you what does it profit a man if he
gained this whole world and yet lose his
soul I appeal appeal to
you I appeal to you friends
family everybody I appeal to
[Music]
you follow
Jesus give your heart to
him not in the oh yeah okay I f look at
my brother's example and see what it
means to actually follow Jesus my
brother did not live a double standard
he was not one foot in the world one
foot in the church he followed Jesus and
those of you that know him
know that he was a man of his
word heavenly
father thank you
Lord thank you for allowing me to still
work with my
brother thank you Lord that through his
death there will be people who have come
to know
you thank you that his death is precious
in your
sight so Lord ease our pain ease our
suffering when we cry Lord remind us
that
Shawn when he was alive would look at us
and say what are you crying
for thank you
Jesus for calling Shawn to follow you
the way that he
did May his death glorify your
name in Jesus name we
pray amen
[Applause]
[Music]
Once Upon a Time you
25 walking up the
aisle you made the promise
of bling twice and you were
29 singing
L and I looked up at you for the first
time words fall short that I am sure
there'll never be anyone like
you you're strong like your
father even when you es scared
when I was in
trouble you never left me
there and you love like your
mother like there's nothing to
lose you're an unsung
hero so I sing this song for
you woke up I was
21 and I fell in love
remember how I told you that I search
the world and I found the girl and all
how she reminds me of
you strong like your father
yes going to be worse for you later
[Music]
here so I'll sing this song for
you for all the times I fell down you
sure we how to stand and when we cross
the ocean you're my safe place to
land been on a thousand stages when it's
all s and
down I hope I make you proud of the M
I've become to be strong like my
father even when I'm
scared and when someone's in trouble
I'll never leave them
there and I love like my
mother like there's nothing to
lose you're my own song
Hero and I sing this song for
[Music]
you me a pi is recording
yeah the dream this to be do for dream
act like you act like you dreaming
[Music]
like let my live forever UNH hand me it
is the same hand which you use on eye to
clean th toilet
bow the doodo of
both day and night remain
separate which means that in order for
the moon to
rise the sun Must
Fall yo it's just my nature and you know
I just felt had to look out I don't know
seen you on the street there I mean
worst you finishing off a poem that I
was trying to figure out for like what 2
years I feel like I've known you in
another life or
[Music]
something 1844 was the year oh
yeah from holy to most holy Jesus
did Heavenly
Sanctuary he took that
fight guiding us through Darkness into
light before God's Throne he stands now
interceding for us showing us how
rightous path through Grace we find in
his love we're in time holy to Most Holy
he with Grace in The Heavenly courts he
took his
place Jesus our high priest forever
true in his light we're born a
new was a new
[Music]
begun doing some
gardening ABC of
Education Adam and Eve in the
garden growing some organic stuff you
know don't know how it might do this
this here but we'll
see trying to do watermelon I don't know
what's going to
happen but every year I do tomatoes
cucumbers
eggplant back in the
garden that's all you fight
cancer being occupied
God's
way
heav
he Jesus our high priest forever true in
his light we're
[Music]
born no retreat no
surrender onward through the power of
God here we
go
[Music]
S his light we're born
new we're born
new I am for her food uh yes I am well
let me tell you there's a new
way the way is called the
rooll his
face okay Uncle Sean another
[Music]
demonstration on the
left on the right
man good boy ninja man oh
man nobody said it was
easy no ever said it would be this
[Music]
yo that was the wildest dream I had I
deeply believe it corresponds
to you we can afford to do that
[Music]
but it's not down to
Paradise at least it's
not and if the wind is right you can
Sail Away find tranquility
oh the can can do
Miracles just you wait and
see
[Music]
me it's not
to me and T just chilling in the car you
know just some to
[Music]
we were
walking
in on
a wind you find the
joy again oh the C can do
mirac just wait and see
for
[Music]
me
sailing Takes Me Away
where I always put
it just a dream the wind to carry me
soon I will be
free
fantasy the best of me when I'm saing
all caught up in the
r every word is symphon w't you
believe
me
saing Takes Me Away to where I always
stood
[Music]
It Dream the you car me soon I will be
free
[Music]
it's
not
not the wind is right you sail away find
Serenity oh the can can do
Miracles just to wait and see
[Music]
sailing Takes Me Away to where I
always dream the wind to carry me soon I
will be
[Music]
[Applause]
good afternoon again
family we're going to make a slight
adjustment to the program uh the remarks
and Reflections will occur uh in the
repass we'll have now is a musical
selection by San Savannah the pastor
will offer the final prayer and then I'm
going to ask everyone to please be
seated while the immediate family leaves
so again just a slight adjustment your
Reflections and your comments will occur
during the repass thank you so
much for
[Music]
yeah just turn it to
you
[Music]
see my hands and look at my
feet it's okay it's hard to
[Music]
believe I have faith you will do greater
things
things it's my time to
go but before
I go tell the world about
me I was dead but now I
live I've got to go now for
little while
but goodbye is not the
end don't forget the things that I
taught
you I coner death and I hold the
keys where I go you will go to
somay but there's much to do
here before you
leave
so go tell the world about
[Music]
me I was dead but now I
live I've got to go now for a
little
while but goodbye is not the end of the
journey the end of the
road my spirit is with you
wherever you
go you have a
purpose and I have a
plan I'll make you this promise I'll
come back
[Music]
again but until
then go tell the world about
me I was de now I
live oh I got to go now for a
little
while but goodbye is not the
end wo
go tell them
[Music]
about I've got it go go tell the world
for a
[Music]
little but goodbye is not the
end thank you
before I pray I just want to thank
Pastor Myers for the
message and all the participants and um
on behalf of the PMA conference
Administration um we want to extend our
condolence to you along with our uh our
family my wife is there and so um we
want you to know that we're praying for
you and um you
are precious to us and so anyways let us
all stand together as we
pray our father and our God
we come to you Lord in the name of Jesus
Christ and we do it in
faith knowing that he is coming
soon and he will put an end to Death and
sorrow and crying in
pain and so
Lord help us to be
faithful help us to have you in our
hearts in our minds every
day help us Lord to live for
you we pray one more time in a very
special way that you may surround the
Myers family with your
comfort and be with them
Lord give them
strength thank you we pray all these
things in Jesus name amen amen you may
be seated
again as a reminder let's allow the
immediate family to exit they will greet
you on your way out and the fellowship
meal is downstairs in the fellowship
hall let's allow the family
to depart
[Music]
God sent his
son they called him
Jesus he came to
love heal and forgive
[Music]
he lived and
died to buy my
[Music]
paron un
empty grave is there to prove my
savior
[Music]
Liv because
He
Lives I Can Face
tomorrow
because he
lives all fear is
gone
because I know
[Music]
oh he holds the
future and life is worth the
Living Just
Because He
Lives how sweet to
hold a
newborn baby
[Music]
baby and feel the
pride and joy he
gives but
greater
still the calm
Assurance this child can face un sh T
days because he
lives
Because He
Lives I Can Face
[Music]
Tomorrow be because he lives
all fear is
gone because I
no he holds the
future and life is worth the
Living Just Because He Lives
and then one
day I'll cross that
River I'll fight life's
[Music]
F no war with
pain
but as
gives way to
Victory I'll see the light of
glory and I'll know He
reigns
Because He
Lives I Can Face Tom more
tomorrow
because he
[Music]
lives all fear is
gone because I
[Music]
know he holds the
F and life is worth the
living just because he
lives and life is worth the
living
just
because he Liv
okay